時は戦国、乱世の時代。
からくり人の住むジパング国では群雄割拠して合戦に明け暮れ、
からくり武芸者たちも勝利と栄光を目指してしのぎを削っていた。
そしていま、からくり武芸者ナンバー１を目指す、とてつもないヒーローが誕生した！
ムサシ、見参でござるだス！
からくり剣豪伝ムサシロード
男はいつでも　世界の真ん中で
いちばん　強くなる日を
AH! AH! 夢見て
心の刃　大空にふりかざし
冒険の旅の　幕を開ける
ジパング国を　さすらう剣豪
その名　からくりびと　ムサシ
GO! FIGHT!
鍔迫り合いの音が
眩しい人生
戦い　昨日よりも　今日　強い
BUGEI! 二刀流　ムサシ
明日は　輝くぞ
鍔迫り合いの音が
眩しい人生
戦い　思い切りと　静けさと
BUGEI! 二刀流　ムサシ
みけんが　きらめいた　ムサシ！！
시라누이 일족의 본거지가 있다고 하는 운젠 산에 향한 무사시는 시라누이의 겐바에게 당했다.
Musashi headed to Mt. Unzen where Shiranui Clan's base is told to be at, but he was attacked by Shiranui's Genba.
골짜기에 떨어진 무사시를 구한 건 히미코였다.
Who rescued Musashi after falling to a valley was Himiko.
그러나 지고쿠다니에서 또다시 겐바에게 당한 무사시는 발을 헛디뎌 화구에 떨어지고 만다.
But Musashi has been attacked again by Genba in Jigokudani, and he fells into a crater.
무사시여, 넌 정말로 죽고 말았는가!
Musashi, are you truly dead?!
역시 불사신
무사시이오
Of Course!
Musashi is Immortal
무사시!
Musashi!
무사시 님!
Mr. Musashi!
무사시! 살아 있으면 답 정도는 해라!
Musashi! Answer us if you're alive!
나 때문에 무사시가 죽었어!
Musashi died because of me!
걱정 마세요, 센히메 님. 게걸스런 무사시가 이 정도로 죽을 리가 없습니다!
Don't worry, Senhime. That glutenous Musashi can't possibly die only by this!
그렇지? 무사시가 죽을 리가 없지?
That must be true! There's no way Musashi can die!
여, 여기에 있는 건 위험합니다. 어서 피난해야!
I- it is dangerous to be here. We have to move!
센히메 님, 어서!
Senhime, hurry!
그래도, 무사시가!
But, Musashi's still there!
어서!
Hurry!
무사시!
Musashi!
무사시 님!
Mr. Musashi!
무사시, 정신 차려, 무사시!
Musashi! Wake up, Musashi!
어떻소. 무사시 군의 상태는.
How is he-gowasu? How's Musashi doing?
가능한 만큼은 전부 하였지만 앞으로는 환자의 기력에 달려 있습니다.
I did everything I could, but the rest is up to the patient's energy.
그런! 무사시, 죽으면 용서 못 해! 뭐야, 거짓말쟁이!
No way! Musashi, I will never forgive you if you die! Were you a liar, after all?!
함께 시라누이를 쓰러트리자며! 무예 대회에서 우승하겠다며!
You said we're going to take Shiranui down together! You said you're gonna be a champion in the martial arts competition!
단고 500그릇 먹기에 도전한 놈답지 않잖아!
That is not expected from someone who can eat 500 dishes of dangos at once!
이대로 죽으면 용서하지 않을 거야!
I won't forgive you if you die like this!
절대 용서 못 할 테니까!
I will never forgive you!
무사시!
Musashi!
무사시 님!
Mr. Musashi!
무사시!
Musashi!
어? 여긴 대체 어디이오?
Huh? Where am I-dasu?
우와, 예쁜 꽃밭이오!
Woah, it's a pretty flower field-dasu!
뭣이오? 어라?
What is that? Huh?
와! 무지개 다리이오!
Look! The rainbow bridge-dasu!
어라, 할아버지, 여긴 어디이오?
Hey, old man! What is this place-dasu?
여긴 말이다, 삼도내인 게 당연하잖냐.
It's obvious that this is the Sanzu River.
삼도내? 그럼 나 죽고 만 것이오?!
Sanzu River?! Then does that mean I died-dasu?!
아니, 아직 완전히 죽은 건 아니다. 저 무지개 다리를 건너서 건너편에 가지 않으면.
No, you're not completely dead yet, unless you go over that rainbow bridge.
그런 것이었소. 그런데 할아버지는 왜 이런 곳에 있소?
I see now! By the way, why are you here, old man-dasu?
난 이 삼도내를 건너게 해 주었지만 이 무지개 다리가 만들어진 덕에 지금은 할 일이 없어졌다.
I used to let people pass this river, but ever since this rainbow bridge was built, I have no job.
무사시!
Musashi!
아, 모두가 부르고 있소. 그럼 할아버지, 나 이제 돌아가오!
Oh, everyone's calling me-dasu. Then, old man, I'll go back-dasu!
좋은 냄새가 나오!
That's a good smell-dasu!
우와, 단고 꽃이오! 이얏호!
Those are dango flowers-dasu! Yeah!
임종입니다.
He has passed away.
무사시!
Musashi!
이거 맛있소! 느긋히 갈 수 있겠소!
These are great! I guess I can take some time eating-dasu!
환영합니다!
Welcome!
도, 도깨비이오!
M- monsters-dasu!
당신이 오기를 기다리고 있었습니다.
We were waiting for you to come.
아니, 그렇게 기뻐해 준다면 나도 기쁘오.
Well, if you're so happy that I'm here, then I'm happy too-dasu!
그럼 가요.
Then let's go.
간다니 어디에오?
Go, to where-dasu?
당신을 위해 환영 파티가 준비되어 있어요.
A welcoming party is prepared just for you!
파티?
Party?
그래도 단고...!
But the dangos...!
먹을거리도 잔뜩 준비되어 있어요!
There will be food that you can eat!
와, 가오, 가오, 꼭 가오!
Yes! I'll go, I'll go! I will go-dasu!
거대한 방이오. 여기서 파티를 하오?
What a big room-dasu! Are we having a party here-dasu?
쉿! 조용히!
Shh! Silence!
염라대왕님 나오십니다!
The King of Hell is coming out!
-어? 염라대왕님?
-자세가 높아!
-What? The King of Hell?
-Get down!
고개를 들거라.
Raise your head.
어! 슈텐타이가!
What?! Shutentiger!
이 자는 이전에 무사시에게 쓰러진 한조의 부하이다.
This guy is one of Hanzō's subordinates, who has been taken down by Musashi.
오니히메!
Onihime!
그리고 이 자는 한조의 부하였지만 한조의 배신으로 죽고 말았다.
And this guy used to be one of Hanzō's subordinates, but she died because of Hanzō's betrayal.
코지로 님은 건강합니까?
Is Mr. Kojirō living well?
예, 예, 건강하오.
Y- yes, he is good-dasu.
근데 왜 너희들이 여기에 있소?!
But why are you guys here-dasu?!
바보 자식. 여기는 영계. 죽은 자가 오는 곳이다.
You fool. This is the spiritual world, where dead people come.
염라대왕을 쫒아내고 지금은 우리가 여길 지배하고 있다.
We throw the King of Hell out of his place, and now we're ruling over this place.
뭣이오?!
What did you say-dasu?!
날 속였겠소!
You fooled me-dasu!
미안해요.
We're sorry.
무사시, 넌 재판 필요 없다. 지옥행이다.
Musashi, you do not need a trial. You're going to hell.
농담 마시오! 나 돌아가오!
Don't fool around-dasu! I'm going back-dasu!
그렇게는 안 된다. 마루여, 무사시를 잡아라!
That will not happen. Floor, catch Musashi!
내가 죽다니 재미 없는 농담이오!
I'm dead? That's bad joke-dasu!
뭣이오!
What's this-dasu?!
마루에서 손이 나왔소!
There's a hand coming out from the floor-dasu!
별 것 아니오!
That was nothing-dasu!
그러기 없기오!
That's cruel-dasu!
젠장! 놓아! 놓으시오!
Damn! Unhand me! Let me go-dasu!
그 대단한 무사시도 염라장부 앞에선 어쩔 수 없구나.
Even that great Musashi can't resist the Register of Hell.
어이, 너희.
Hey, you people.
-예!
-이 놈을 지옥에 데려가서 팽하는 벌에 처해라.
-Yessir!
-Take this guy to hell and punish him by boiling.
-알겠냐!
-예!
-Did you understand?!
-Yessir!
놓아! 놓으시오!
Unhand me! Put me down-dasu!
나, 아무것도 나쁜 짓 한 게 없소! 지옥에 가고 싶지 않소!
I never did anything wrong-dasu! I don't want to go to hell-dasu!
-뭔가 해 주고 싶어도...
-놓아주면 우리가 팽당할 테니까...
-Even though we want to do something for him...
-We'll be punished by boiling instead of him if we let him go...
왠지 싫은 분위기가 되었소.
I don't like this ambiance-dasu...
어이, 냉큼 일어서지 못할까!
Stand up promptly!
저건 뭘 하는 것이오?
What's going on there?
저건 모래지옥이라는 곳으로 저 무거운 썰매를 영구히 끄는 곳이야.
That is Sand Hell; one has to pull that heavy sleigh for eternity.
지금 썰매를 끌고 있는 자가 원래 염라대왕님이야.
The one who's pulling right now is the true King of Hell.
앉아 졸아 염라장부를 빼앗기지만 않았으면 이렇게는 안 되었을 것을...
If I didn't doze off and hadn't taken away the Register of Hell, this wouldn't have happened...
이게 지옥의 명물, 가마솥의 끓는물이야.
This is one feature of hell, boiling water in cauldron.
조, 조금 온도가 너무 뜨겁지 않소?
I- isn't that water too hot-dasu?
어, 손님이냐!
Oh, it must be a guest!
어?! 너 고에몬도!
Huh? You must be Goemondo!
오, 그러는 너는 무사시!
Oh, and you must be Musashi!
아, 이 사내도 무사시한테 당한 한조의 부하이다.
Er, this guy also is one of Hanzō's subordinates that Musashi took care of.
인연이오, 인연이야! 이런 곳에서 무사시하고 만날 줄이야!
What a destiny! What a fate! I met Musashi at a place like this!
그 때의 복수를 꽉 해 주겠다!
I'll pay you back everything you did to me back then!
아, 아니아니, 걱정 말고 맘대로 하시오.
Err, don't worry, just do whatever you want-dasu.
이런 높은 곳에서 떨어지면 죽고 마오!
If I fall from a high place like this, I'll die-dasu!
바보 자식! 넌 이미 죽었다!
You fool! You're already dead!
게다가 이 가마솥에는 혼을 분리시켜 버리는 뜨거운 물이 들어있으니 말이야.
Moreover, there is a hot water in this cauldron, that will separate your spirit from your body.
그, 그럼 난 이 세상에도 저 세상에도 없는 게 되오?
I- if then, do I not exist both in this and that world-dasu?
그려!
Yeah!
젠장, 그건 싫소!
Damn, I don't like that-dasu!
나, 죽어도 여기선 안 움직이오.
Even if I had to die, I won't move from here-dasu.
그러니까, 너 이미 죽었다니까. 포기할 줄 모르는 놈이군!
Again, you're already dead! Know when to give up!
에잇, 끈질긴 놈!
How persistent of you!
아, 고집이 세군, 고집이 세! 죽은 자는 포기할 줄 아는 게 중요하다!
How tenacious! How stubborn! A dead person must know to give up!
아니, 그럴 리가...
No, that's not true...
간질간질간질간질...
Tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle...
안돼안돼, 안 되오, 그러기 없기오, 안 되오!
No, no, don't do that, please don't do that-dasu, don't-dasu!
에잇, 멈춰라!
Stop right there!
멈추라고 하시는 그 분은?
Who could it be that asking me to stop?
쫓기는 주제에 이름을 대는 것도 어리석지만, 약한 자를 구해, 강한 자를 꺾는 영계의 망나니 이시마츠 님이란
Telling my name when I'm being chased is foolish, but nonetheless,
the one to help the weak and crush the strong is the hooligan of the spiritual world, Ishimatsu...
바로 이 날 말한다!
is right here!
이시마츠 씨!
Mr. Ishimatsu!
네가 최근 이 주변에서 날뛴다는 이시마츠냐!
So, you must be that Ishimatsu messing around recently!
너부터 고통스럽게 만들어 주겠다!
You're gonna suffer pain first!
뜨겁구나, 뜨거워!
How hot! How burning!
이시마츠 씨! 오랜만이오!
Mr. Ishimatsu! It's been a while-dasu!
그려!
Right!
(지옥의 부처: 매우 곤란할 때 도움 받음의 비유)
(Buddha of Hell: idiom; being helped when one's in dire trouble)
지옥의 부처라는 것은 이걸 말하는가! 이시마츠에게 구해진 무사시의 운명은 어찌!
The Buddha of Hell must be him! What will happen to Musashi, rescued by Ishimatsu?
질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
Wait for the stormy latter half!
카라쿠리 검호전 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden: Musashi Road
뭐냐, 그랬냐, 그랬어!
So that's what was going on!
이야, 나 이런 곳에서 이시마츠 씨하고 만나게 될 거라고는 생각도 못 했소!
I never thought I was going to meet Mr. Ishimatsu at a place like this-dasu!
나도 그려. 설마 지팡구 제일의 무예가가 그런 놈한테 당할 거라고는 생각도 안 했다!
Me too! I never thought the best martial artist of Jipangu would be done by a guy like that!
어?
Huh?
자, 내게 지팡구 제일의 실력을 보여 주시라!
Show me the abilities of the best of Jipangu!
그, 그게...
Well, the problem is...
왜 그러냐. 안 부끄러워해도 되잖냐! 아니면 구경꾼이 적으면 할 기분이 안 들더냐?
What's wrong? You don't have to shy! Or, do you feel like showing off only when there are lots of audiences?
사, 사실은, 나, 아직 지팡구 제일의 무예가가 되지 못했소.
T- to be honest, I couldn't become the number one martial artist of Jipangu yet-dasu.
뭐야?! 이 자식, 나하고의 약속을 잊고 잘도 뺀질거리며 이 세상에 왔겠다!
What?! How dare you forget the promise with me and come to this world without any regret?!
나도 오고 싶지 않았소!
I didn't want to come, too-dasu!
사내는 말이다, 한번 약속하면 죽어도 지키는 것이다.
A man must keep his promise even if he dies!
자! 지금 당장 지팡구 제일의 무예가가 되어라!
Here! Become the number one martial artist of Jipangu right now, right here!
그런 소릴 해도 난 이미 죽고 말았소.
No matter what you say, I'm here because I'm already dead-dasu...
아니오, 아직 살아 돌아갈 방법은 있습니다.
No. You still can revive.
어라?! 당신!
Huh? You must be...!
진짜 염라대왕님! 어떻게 여기 있소?
The true King of Hell! Why are you here?
아까 널 구하기 전에 내가 구해냈어.
I rescued him before I rescue you!
그래서, 염라대왕님, 이 얼간이를 되살릴 방법이란?
So, King of Hell, what is that way to revive this dimwit?
네, 육체가 있을 동안 인간계로 돌아가, 몸에 들어가면 됩니다.
One can go back to the human world when there still is body, and get into that body.
뭣이오, 그렇게 간단했소!
Oh, that sounds so easy-dasu!
다만 서둘러야만 합니다.
But you must hurry.
어라? 사이고 씨. 주베 씨.
Huh? Mr. Saigo! Mr. Jūbee!
센짱까지! 대체 누가 죽었소?
Even Sen-chan! Who's dead-dasu?
내 장례식이오!
It's my funeral ceremony-dasu!
이대로 화장되고 만다면 더는 되살아날 수 없게 됩니다. 자, 어서!
If your body gets cremated, then you won't be able to revive anymore. Hurry!
그래도, 나...
But... I...
뭘 하냐. 어서 가라!
What are you doing? Hurry up and leave!
그래도, 나, 슈텐하고 오니히메를 저기에 둘 수는 없소!
But I cannot let Shuten and Onihime be there-dasu!
이 자슥! 저런 놈들 따위는 내가 착착 썰어 해치워 줄 테니까 넌 어서 꺼져라!
You numskull! I'll take care of those bastards, so that you can lightheartedly get lost from this place!
그래도, 저 놈들은 무서운 힘을 가지고 있소!
But they have fearful powers-dasu!
놈들이 무서운 힘을 발휘할 수 있는 것은 제 염라장부를 가지고 있기 때문입니다.
The only reason they can show those powers is because they have my Register of Hell.
염라장부?
Register of Hell?
염라장부는 영계의 법률서로, 염라장부를 가진 자의 명령은 어떤 것이라도 실현합니다.
The Register of Hell is the lawbook of the spiritual world, and it will actualize the order of whoever with that register!
그럼 그 염라장부를 되찾으면 되는 것이오! 좋소, 되살기 전에 막 날뛰어 주겠소!
So it'll work out if we take back that Register of Hell-dasu! Alright, I'll rage before I revive-dasu!
정말, 너란 놈은 어디까지 성격 좋을 셈이냐?
Really, you are excessively credulous!
그래도 나, 이시마츠 씨의 아우이오. 성격 좋은 건 형 닮은 것이오!
But I'm the younger brother of Mr. Ishimatsu-dasu! I'm credulous because my brother is so-dasu!
그래...
Err...
그것도 그렇네!
That makes sense!
그렇소!
Yeah, right-dasu!
그럼 영계성에 서두릅시다!
Then let's hurry ourselves to the castle of the spiritual world!
영계성에 전속력!
Full speed to the castle of the spiritual world!
영계를 지배하고 그 무사시도 지옥에 보내고 오늘 술은 언제보다도 맛있구나!
I'm ruling over the spiritual world, and sent that Musashi to hell! Today's liquor takes better than the usual!
흥, 당신 말야, 술 언제 먹어도 맛있잖아?
Hmph. Doesn't any liquor taste good to you all the time?
그렇네!
That makes sense!
슈텐! 오니히메! 나오시오!
Shuten! Onihime! Get out-dasu!
무사시! 어떻게 돌아왔냐!
Musashi! How did you come back?!
정의의 히로는 불멸이오! 자, 순순히 염라장부를 염라대왕님께 돌려주시오!
The hero of justice is immortal-dasu! Now, you will give the Register of Hell back to the King of Hell!
에잇, 건방진 소리 마라!
You shouldn't be impertinent!
번개여! 놈들을 잿더미로 만들어 버려라!
Dear lightening! Make them into ashes!
나, 아버지하고 번개가 싫소!
I hate fathers and lightnings-dasu!
저 자식들!
Those bastards!
네이놈! 잘도 피했겠다!
How dare you evade that?!
화산이여! 놈들을 날려버려라!
Volcanos! Throw them away!
이천일류 번개검!
Nitenichiryu: Lightening Sword!
해냈소.
I did it-dasu.
이야, 멋지다, 무사시!
You're cool, Musashi!
네이놈들, 더는 용서 못 한다! 하나도 안 남기고 영계에서 지워 버리겠다!
You bastards! You won't be forgiven! I'll remove all of you from the spiritual world!
나, 번개도 화산도 싫지만 납작해지는 건 더 싫소!
I don't like lightening and volcanoes-dasu, but I hate being flat even more-dasu!
어이, 바보 슈텐!
Heya, idiot Shuten!
자, 형, 여기여! 어디 잡을 수 있으면 잡아 보셔!
Hey, bro, I'm over here! Get me if you can!
누굴 바보로 아나!
Are you trying to make a fool out of me?!
어이어이, 여기다, 여기!
Heya, hey, over here, here!
어이, 아둔패기 머저리, 여기다, 여기!
Hey, you foolish dunces, over here, here!
이시마츠 씨!
Mr. Ishimatsu!
위험해, 위험해!
That was close!
분해!
That was so damn close!
멈춰!
Stop!
이대로는 전멸하고 맙니다.
We'll be annihilated at this rate.
무사시, 우리가 이목을 끌 테니까 넌 염라장부를 빼앗아라!
Musashi, while we get attraction from them, you go get the Register of Hell!
알겠소!
Roger-dasu!
뭐야?!
What?!
젠장, 어딜 간 거야?!
Damn, where did they go to?!
숨어도 소용 없어. 찾으면 짓밟아 주겠다.
No use hiding. I'll stomp over everywhere!
어이! 귀 얇은 거인들! 어딜 보냐, 이 낙지 놈들!
Hey, you giant dolts! Where are you looking at, you squids?!
이 자식, 누굴 바보로 알고!
How dare you treat us like fools?!
여기다, 여기!
Over here! Here!
어이, 여기여!
Hey, I'm here!
여기, 여기!
Here, here!
머리 돌리기도 힘들지?
Turning your head must be difficult!
아따, 여기라니까!
Again, I'm over here!
여기여!
Here!
어이어이!
Heya, hey!
어딘지 모르겠지?
You can't get us!
어이, 여기야, 여기!
Hey, over here, hey!
흥, 바보 자식.
Hmph. You fool.
아야!
Ouch!
뭔 짓이야! 아프잖아!
What was that for?! That hurt!
그게 네 발 위에 무사시가...
Well, Musashi was on your foot!
뭐야?!
What?!
이 자식!
You bastard!
복수할 필요는 없잖아!
There was no need to pay back!
아니, 거기에 이시마츠가...
No, there was Ishimatsu!
속보이는 입놀림 하지 마라!
Don't try to fool me when it's written on your face!
뭐?! 또 말해 봐라!
What?! Say that again!
찾았소! 이거겠소, 염라장부!
I found it-dasu! This must be the Register of Hell-dasu!
맞습니다! 어서 여기에!
That's right! Throw it to here!
저런!
Oh no!
가오!
Here it goes-dasu!
염라장부요, 최후의 힘을 써서 오니히메와 슈텐을 무한지옥에 보내 버려라!
Dear Register of Hell, use your last powers to send Onihime and Shuten into the hell of infinite suffering!
해냈구나, 무사시! 그 근성이 있으면 분명 지팡구 제일이 될 거다!
You did it, Musashi! With that kind of guts, you will end up becoming the number one of Jipangu!
이시마츠 씨!
Mr. Ishimatsu!
자, 무사시 씨, 서두르세요. 지상에서는 당신의 화장이 시작되려 합니다.
Now, Mr. Musashi, hurry up. Your cremation is about to begin on the ground.
으악! 몸이 타 버리면 되살아날 수 없게 되어 버리오!
Wah! If my body ends up burnt, then I won't be able to revive anymore-dasu!
뭐, 뭘 하냐! 어서 꺼져라!
W- what are you doing! Get lost immediately!
아, 알겠소!
G- got it-dasu!
지팡구 제일의 무예가가 될 때까지 다시는 돌아오지 마라!
Never come back until you become the number one martial artist of Jipangu!
맡겨 두시오! 나, 이시마츠 씨의 아우이오!
Leave it to me-dasu! I am your younger brother-dasu, Mr. Ishimatsu!
저 자식, 청춘이네!
His youth is great!
드디어 작별이네 무사시.
Time to bid farewell, Musashi.
무지개 다리이오!
It's the rainbow bridge-dasu!
무사시. 네 무예가 제일의 꿈은 내가 확실히 이어받아 주겠다. 넌 성불해라.
Musashi. I will inherit your dreams of becoming the best of martial artists. You may enter Nirvana and rest in peace.
돌아왔소!
I'm back!
아, 돌아왔구나.
Welcome back.
뜨거!
Hot!
무사시! 그새 둔갑해 나왔구나! 어서 성불해라!
Musashi! You became a ghost already?! Get lost to Nirvana immediately!
아, 아니오! 나 정말 살아 돌아왔소!
N- no! I really revied-dasu!
아, 살아 돌아왔더니 배가 고프오.
That reviving really made me hungry-dasu...
아! 만두이오!
Hey! Dumplings-dasu!
굿 타이밍!
Good timing!
맛있소!
It's tasty-dasu!
이, 이 게걸스러움은 어딜 봐도 정말 살아 돌아왔다고밖에.
T- that gluttony could be done only if that's truly revived Musashi.
음, 맛있소!
Yes! So tasty!
한번 죽은 무사시. 그렇지만 이시마츠와의 우정으로 되살아나는 게 가능했다.
Musashi had died once. But thanks to the friendship with Ishimatsu, he managed to revive.
그 우정에 답하기 위해서라도, 힘내라, 무사시! 싸워라, 무사시! 지팡구 제일의 무예가가 되어라!
To respond to that friendship, go for it, Musashi! Fight, Musashi! Become the number one martial artist of Jipangu!
カラのポケットに　ツキが
飛び込むことも　あるさ
おっきな声で　笑えば
あしたには　朝が来る
無くすものなんか　何もないさ
やっちゃえ！イケイケ！
手ぶらは　強いぜ
てなもんだ　のーてんきに行こう
人生　てなもんさ　チャンスが　ほら
しっぽを振って　追ってくるぜ
てなもんだ　のーてんきに行こう
未来も　てなもんさ　あしたが　ほら
両手ひろげて　笑ってるぜ
살아돌아와 다행이오! 단고도 잔뜩 먹어서 정말 기쁘오!
It is great to be revived-dasu! After eating lots of dangos, I'm so happy-dasu!
그런데 시라누이 놈들, 또 우리한테 덤비러 왔소.
But those Shiranui bastards came to attack us again-dasu!
지라이얀과 함게 해치웠지만 지라이얀이 히미코 씨가 시라누이의 여왕이라고 하오.
While I've taken them down with Jiraiyan, he's saying that Ms. Himiko is the queen of SHiranui!
다음 이야기! 비밀의 히미코 씨이오
Next story! Mysterious Ms. Himiko
질풍노도의 짱뚱어이오!
It's a stormy mudskipper-dasu!
다음 이야기
비밀의
히미코 씨이오!
기대하세요!
Next Episode
Mysterious
Ms. Himiko
Look forwards for it!